Get started

Get started

Privacy Policy
==============

_Effective Date: May 17, 2024_

Hi there! At Zeta Help Inc. (“Zeta”, “we”, “us” or “our”), we’re committed to maintaining your confidence and trust. As part of that commitment, we want you to understand our personal information practices. This Privacy Policy (or this “Policy”) is provided to you to explain how we collect, use, and disclose personal information about you in connection with your use of our services including our website at [https://www.askzeta.com/](https://www.askzeta.com/) (or other of our websites that may link to this Policy), as well as our mobile apps, deposit account, payment cards, online worksheets, and any other services we may offer (collectively referred to as our “Services”).

By using or accessing our Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies described in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use and share your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

You may print a copy of this Privacy Policy by pressing print on your browser. If you have a disability and need to access or receive a copy of this Privacy Policy by alternative means, please contact us at legal@askzeta.com.

In reviewing this Privacy Policy, please keep in mind the following points:

* Our use of your personal information may vary depending on what Services you use and how you use them. For some Services, we may provide you with additional notices about your privacy or our collection and use of your personal information. If there is any conflict between two of our privacy notices, the notice that is more specific to a Service will control with respect to that Service.
    
* Personal information required to open a Zeta Account through our banking partners (“Customer Deposit Account Data”) is collected by both Zeta and the relevant banking partner, and both Zeta and the banking partner will have independent access and control over use of this information. This policy outlines how Zeta handles your Customer Deposit Account Data, but Zeta does not control how our banking partners use your Customer Deposit Account Data. For those using services involving our banking partner Piermont Bank, please refer to the [Zeta-Piermont Account Agreement](https://www.askzeta.com/zeta-piermont-account-agreement) and [Piermont Bank Privacy Policy](https://www.piermontbank.com/privacy-policy/) for information concerning Piermont Bank’s treatment of personal information.
    
* Zeta uses Plaid Technologies, Inc. (“Plaid”) to gather user data from financial institutions. In order to use certain of our Services, you will be required to grant Zeta and Plaid the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from the relevant financial institution, and your personal information will be transferred, stored, and processed by Plaid in accordance with the [Plaid Privacy Policy](https://plaid.com/overview-privacy/).
    
* As indicated in our Terms of Use, Zeta uses Astra Inc ("Astra") for our instant payment functionality. You agree to your personal information being transferred to Astra, and being stored and processed by Astra in accordance with Astra's Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. Please refer to those documents for more complete information about how Astra collects, uses, and discloses information about you.
    
* “Personal information” is used in this Privacy Policy to refer to any information that relates to a specific natural person, who may be identified in or reasonably identifiable based on the information.
    
* If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our information practices, please contact us at support@askzeta.com.

1\. **How We Collect, Use and Share Personal Information**
==========================================================

A. **Personal Information We Collect**
--------------------------------------

Zeta collects personal information for a variety of purposes, and the kinds of personal information that we collect about you depends on how you use or interact with our Services. (For example, personal information we collect about website visitors is different from the personal information we collect about mobile app users.)

Depending on how you use or interact with our Services, we may collect the following kinds of personal information about you:

* _Personal identifiers, contact and biographical information_. This is personal information such as your name, home address, e-mail address, or telephone number, as well as demographic information, such as gender and date of birth, your photograph, or information about your employment, finances, interests, and activities. (For this kind of information, you’ll know what we collect because we’ll collect it from you directly.)
    
* _Government identification information_. This includes your Social Security number, driver’s license number, or ID numbers from other government documents, and for some Services, we may collect copies of government-issued photo IDs, such as a driver’s license or passport.
    
* _Payment information_. We may collect credit card information or other means of payment, if you use any Services that require payments.
    
* _Financial information_. This includes information about your income, expenses, transactions, or debt, or your credit score and other information from your credit report. If you choose to connect a bank account to Zeta, we will also collect financial account numbers, transaction information, account balances, and other information about your banking activities that you or your bank may make available to us.
    
* _Social media handles_. If you contact us through a social media platform, we may collect your username or social media handle, or other information about you that is available on social media.

The information described above is generally collected directly from users of our Services – as when you submit information to us through our website, mobile apps, or other Services that we offer.

In some of the cases described above, we will collect information from third parties – from your bank or other financial services you use, from credit reporting agencies, or through social media sites. We may also collect personal information about you from an identity verification service, if you request Services that require us to confirm your identity, and if your traditional ID (such as a driver’s license) cannot be verified, or if there are other issues confirming your identity.

In addition to the personal information described above, we also collect information automatically, whenever any person visits our website or uses our other Services. This automated technical information, which may also be personal information about you, includes:

* _Technical and usage information__._ When you visit and navigate through the Zeta website, mobile apps or other Services, we automatically collect technical and usage information about your computer or device, and your activities when you interact with our Services, such as your IP address, device identifiers, browser type, geolocation information, operating system, web pages that visit before and after accessing Zeta webpages, the specific Zeta webpages, links, or features you viewed or used and the times those were viewed or used, and other usage statistics and “clickstream” data.
    
* _Data collected through cookies, pixel tags and similar technologies__._ A cookie is a small text file stored on your computer or device when you visit our website or other Services. We use cookies to identify you or your device to our Services, and for security purposes, to facilitate site navigation, to perform analytics, and to personalize your experience while visiting the website. We also use pixel tags, which are small files embedded in webpages and email. We use pixel tags to track whether users visit specific pages of the website, downloaded a particular document, or opened a Zeta email.

B. **Use of Personal Information**
----------------------------------

_To provide the Services and operate our business._ We generally use the personal information we collect to manage and operate our business, and to provide our Services, as described in the following purposes of use:

* To provide our Services, including the Zeta mobile app, as well as our websites, blogs, and other content that we produce.
    
* To communicate with users of our Services, including communications that are part of the use of the Services as well as other administrative communications.
    
* To verify your identity where it’s necessary to do so to provide our Services.
    
* To facilitate banking or other financial transactions for users of our Services.
    
* To provide customer support and customer service, including answering any questions and responding to requests that we receive.
    
* For payment purposes, if you use any Services that require payments.
    
* For marketing purposes, including communications about Zeta’s Services, company developments and news, or about other third-party products or services that you may be interested in.
    
* For internal business operations and business management.
    
* To perform research and analysis, which is used to develop and improve our Services and the delivery of our Services, or to better understand our users’ interest in third-party products and services.

_For legal, safety, and security purposes._  We may also use personal information to comply with law or for safety and security reasons, as follows:

* We may use and share personal information as we believe necessary or appropriate to comply with laws that apply to Zeta and to support our bank partners’ compliance with applicable law, including anti-money laundering (AML) and sanctions screening rules.
    
* We may use and share personal information to respond to lawful requests and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities.
    
* We may use personal information and disclose it to law enforcement, government authorities, and private parties as we believe necessary or appropriate to: (i) protect our or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property (including by making and defending legal claims); (ii) audit our internal processes for compliance with legal and contractual requirements; (iii) enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Services; and (iv) prevent, identify, investigate and deter fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity, including cyberattacks and identity theft.

_To create anonymous data._ We also use personal information to generate aggregated, de-identified or otherwise anonymous data, which does not directly identify and could not reasonably be used to identify any specific individual. We use this anonymous data to understand, develop, improve, and market our Services, and it may be used or shared with third parties for any lawful purpose.

_For other disclosed purposes and with consent._ We may also use personal information for other purposes that are disclosed at the time you provide personal information, or purposes where we obtain your consent.

C. **How We Share or Disclose Personal Information**
----------------------------------------------------

Depending on how you use or interact with our Services, we may share personal information with third parties as follows:

* _Service providers__._ We share personal information with third-party service providers that perform business-related functions on our behalf, such as website hosting and support, conducting research and data analysis for us, and performing marketing functions for us. We will only disclose personal information to service providers as needed for them to provide services.Our service providers are only permitted to use this personal information on our behalf, to provide services, and they are obligated to protect the confidentiality of personal information.
    
* _Affiliated companies__._ We may share your personal information with our affiliated companies, as permitted by law, for research and analysis purposes. Your personal information will not be used by our affiliated companies to market directly to you or to establish your creditworthiness or eligibility for products or services that they may offer unless explicitly stated.
    
* _Bank partners and other partner organizations__._ When you use certain of our Services, we will need to share your personal information with our partner banks, such as Piermont Bank, or technology providers, such as Plaid Technologies, Inc., and those partners will maintain and independently control copies of your personal information.For example, Zeta Account information is shared with our partner bank, Piermont Bank. 
    
* _Business transfers__._ We may share your personal information with another entity during the negotiation of or as a result of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale or other change of control of our business. In the event that such a transaction occurs, your personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the other entity.
    
* _As required by law_. We may use and share personal information as we believe necessary or appropriate to comply with laws that apply to Zeta and to support our bank partners’ compliance with applicable law, and to respond to lawful requests and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities.
    
* _For legal, compliance, safety, and security purposes__._ We may use personal information and disclose it to law enforcement, government authorities, and private parties as we believe necessary or appropriate to: (i) protect our or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property (including by making and defending legal claims); (ii) audit our internal processes for compliance with legal and contractual requirements; (iii) enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Services; and (iv) prevent, identify, investigate and deter fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity, including cyberattacks and identity theft.
    
* _At your direction or with your consent._ We may also share your personal information with third parties at your direction or with your consent.

_No sale of personal information._ We disclose the categories of personal information as described above for our business purposes. We do not sell personal information to third parties.

_No disclosures for third parties’ direct marketing._ It is our policy not to provide your personal information to third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes, without your consent.

D. **How Long We Keep Personal Information**
--------------------------------------------

We retain personal data about you for as long as you have an open account with us or as otherwise necessary to provide you with our Services. In some cases, we retain personal information for longer, if doing so is necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes or collect fees owed, or is otherwise permitted or required by applicable law, rule or regulation. We may further retain anonymous or aggregated information, in a form that does not and could not reasonably be used to identify any specific individual.

2\. **Your Choices**
====================

In your use and interaction with our Services, you have certain choices and controls with respect to the use of your personal information, which are described here.

* _Update Your Personal Information__._ If your personal information changes (for example, to change your email address), you can update the information in the following ways:
    
    * Zeta supports information changes to be handled directly through the Zeta App.
        
    * All other information can be changed directly on your profile by emailing us at support@askzeta.com.

We may require additional documentation to help identify you before we are able to make personal information changes.

* _Choose not to provide personal information or not use the Services__._ You can always decide not to provide us with personal information or not to use certain Services that require your personal information. But please understand that if you choose not to provide personal information to us, you may not be able to create an online account with Zeta or use Services that we offer.
    
* _Opt out of marketing emails__._ We may use your name and email address to send Zeta-related promotional emails to you. You can direct us to stop sending promotional emails by following the “unsubscribe” or similar instructions that are included in any Zeta-related promotional email you receive. Your opt-out request will be processed within 30 days of the date on which we receive it. Please understand that, even if you opt out of marketing emails, you will still receive service-related, account-related, or other non-promotional emails from Zeta.
    
* _Delete or close your account__._ You close your Zeta Account by following the process outlined in the “CLOSE ACCOUNT” tab from the settings menu in the Zeta app. After you delete your account, you will not be able to log into the Zeta App or access any of your Personal Information. After you close your account, we will work to remove your information from our systems. However, it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your personal information, as personal information may be retained to comply with legal requirements or for necessary business functions, or may remain in archival data. Also, if we have previously shared your information with partner organizations as described in this Privacy Policy, those companies may not be required to delete your information. (You can open a new account at any time, if you choose to do so.)
    
* _Cookies_. As described in this Privacy Policy, we use cookies to gather information and enhance users’ experience of the Services. You may configure your internet browser to reject or disable cookies, as described in documentation for your browser. Please understand, however, that rejecting or disabling cookies may affect your experience of our website or other Services, or interfere with your ability to access our Services.
    
* _Online advertising__._ We may also participate in online advertising networks that collect personal information. Many advertising networks offer means to opt out of targeted advertising. More information about targeted advertising is available at [https://thenai.org/](https://thenai.org/), and opt-out resources are available at [https://optout.networkadvertising.org/](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

_We do not respond to “Do-Not-Track” requests__._ Some internet browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit. However, no industry-standard Do-Not-Track protocol has not yet been established, and we currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” or similar signals sent to our Site. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

3\. **Security of Your Personal Information**
=============================================

We take information security seriously, and we have implemented an information security program that includes physical, technical, and procedural safeguards that are reasonably designed to protect the personal information that we collect or that you may provide to us.

We restrict access to personal information to only authorized employees for permitted business purposes, and we require our third-party service providers to protect your personal information and use it exclusively for the purpose of performing certain business functions on our behalf.

However, no electronic data transmission or storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Although we take steps to secure your information, we cannot ensure or promise that the information you transmit to us will remain secure.

_You are also responsible for the security of your Zeta account._ You also need to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information too. You should be careful in how you share personal information with others and avoid sending any sensitive personal information through unsecure, unencrypted email. Do not provide your username and password to the Zeta website or apps to others. If you become aware of any suspicious activity associated with any of your Zeta accounts, contact us immediately at support@askzeta.com.

4\. **Children's Personal Information**
=======================================

Zeta’s Services, including our website, and web and mobile apps, are not directed to children. We do not knowingly collect personal information through the Services from children younger than 13 years of age. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child younger than 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information without his or her consent, he or she should contact us at support@askzeta.com. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personally identifiable information from a child younger than 13 years of age, we will make reasonable efforts to delete such information from our records.

5\. **Internal Data Transfers**
===============================

We maintain offices and facilities in the United States, and personal information may be transferred to the United States or other locations outside of your state, province, or country of residence, where privacy laws may not be as protective as those in the state, province, or country you resides.

6\. **Updates to This Privacy Policy**
======================================

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our information practices. If we make material changes to the Privacy Policy, we will provide notification by updating the “Effective Date” date at the top of the Privacy Policy and posting the new Privacy Policy to our website or other Services. We may also notify you about updates through email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or use other reasonable means to alert you to changes. We encourage you to periodically review the Zeta website or app for the latest information on our privacy practices.

7\. **Questions? How to Contact Us**
====================================

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our data practices, please contact us in-app or at support@askzeta.com. We can also be contacted via postal mail at:

2261 Market Street #4718 San Francisco, CA 94114 United States

A newsletter designed to help  
you achieve relationship goals.

A newsletter designed to help you achieve relationship goals.

Join Our Community

© 2024 Zeta Help Inc. All rights reserved.

2261 Market Street #4718

San Francisco, CA 94114

Join Our Community

© 2024 Zeta Help Inc. All rights reserved.

2261 Market Street #4718

San Francisco, CA 94114

* * *

To safely consume this site, we recommend reading this disclaimer. Any outbound links will take you away from Zeta, to external sites in the world wide web. Just so you know, Zeta doesn’t endorse any linked websites nor do we pay/bribe anyone to appear on here. Any reference to prices on the site are just estimates; actual prices are up to specific merchants and their current desire to charge you for things. Also, nothing on this website should be construed as investment advice. We’re here to share our favorite tools, tactics and tips for managing your money together. This content is for your responsible consumption. Please don’t see this as a recommendation to buy specific investments or go on a crypto-binge. Lastly, we 100% believe that personal finance is exactly that, personal. We may sometimes publish content on this website that has been created by affiliated or unaffiliated partners such as employees, advisors or writers. Unless we explicitly say so, these post do not necessarily represent the actual views or opinions of Zeta.  
  
By using this website, you understand the content presented is provided for informational purposes only and agree to our [Terms of Use](https://www.askzeta.com/terms-of-use) and [Privacy Policy](https://www.askzeta.com/privacy-policy).  
  
1Zeta is a financial technology company, not a bank. Banking services provided by Piermont Bank; Member FDIC. All deposit accounts of the same ownership and/or vesting held at the issuing bank are combined and insured under an FDIC Certificate of $250,000 per depositor. The Zeta Mastercard® Debit Card is issued by Piermont Bank, Member FDIC, pursuant to license by Mastercard International Incorporated and can be used everywhere Mastercard is accepted.  
  
2Zeta Annual Percentage Yield (APY) is effective as of 05/01/2023, for customers who qualify for VIP status. Minimum amount to open an account is $0.00. Minimum balance to earn the APY is $0.01. Interest rates are as follows: 2.45% APY applies to the entire balance for customers who qualify for VIP status. Interest rates may change after the account is opened. Fees may reduce earnings.
